Systems engineer / Software developer Yeison Betancourt Solis C.C 1.115.080.936 Buga - Valle 30 Years old





PHONE

(+57) 316 279 3738



EMAIL

yeisonbe10@hotmail.com



WEBSITE

<u>Portafolio</u>



LINKEDIN Perfil

Profile

I'm a FullStack developer from Valle University with four years of experience in software development for the technology sector. I'm looking to collaborate in a position as an application developer since I have experience in different web and mobile projects.

I have skills for cooperative and team work, I'm proactive, responsible and with fast learning ability. Interested in the development of web applications, mobile app and project management.

Professional Experiences

☐ September 2019 - Present

Software Engineer

Fullstack Labs +57 (5) 385-1980

Development for web and mobile with international clients projects

☐ February 2019 - September 2019

Development Engineer

CETOCO SAS 3187348993

Development for web and mobile applications

☐ August 2016 - February 2019

Development Engineer

ADATEC 3707777

Development and implementation for web and mobile applications

☐ September 2015 – August 2016

Development Engineer

ARQUITECSOFT 3797724

Development and implementation of the new requirements requested for the application

Education

2016

Information Systems Engineering

UNIVERSIDAD DEL VALLE - CALI / COLOMBIA

8. Semester - August - December 2014

□ 2010

Secondary education

TULIO ENRIQUE TASCÓN - BUGA / COLOMBIA

Engineering Stacks

PROGRAMMING:

ES6, JavaScript, TypeScript, React, React Native, Redux, GraphQL, Ruby, C#, C++, PHP, .NET

FRAMEWORKS:

Angular, Ionic, AngularJS, Vue, NodeJS, NestJS, NextJS, Go, Visual Studio, YII, Laravel, JDeveloper, Yeoman, Joomla, Wordpress, PrestaShop

VERSION CONTROL:

Git, Bitbucket, SVN

KNOWLEDGE:

Movil, Frontend, Backend, CI/CD, AWS services, relational databases, non-relational databases

COURSES

- English (High intermediate B1+) Centro Cultural Colombo Americano
- React JS + redux + ES6 Udemy
- Vue JS + Firebase Udemy
- Angular Udemy
- Information security Icesi University
- Basic Programming Platzi
- Programming Websites with HTML and JAVASCRIPT Sena Virtual
- Computer Design of databases in SQL Sena Virtual
- Computer architecture Sena Virtual
- C++ Sena Virtual
- MicrosoftOffice and OpenOffice

Projects

- Portfolio Web with GitHub Pages http://betancourtyeison.github.io/
- Angular applications
- Vue JS applications
- React applications
- Websites with Responsive Design
- Java applications like Sodoku and LunarLand
- Refrastrabe company Guacari Valle http://refrastrabe.com/
- Refratek company http://refratek.com/







References

Name: Juan Carlos Renteria Company: Refrastrabe S.A.S.

Job title: CEO **Phone:** 310 836 0100

Name: Oscar Fernando Betancourt

Company: CVC - Corporación autónoma regional del valle del cauca

Job title: Systems analyst **Phone:** 322 613 2940

Name: Jorge Arley Castaño Company: Monetta Job title: CTO

Phone: 315 555 4340

